ADAPTED FROM DEMON KING
OF JINJIANG LITERATURE CITY
ORIGINAL WORK BY JIULU FEIXIANG
Why do I feel so bad?
I knew we would be apart.
I shouldn't have let him stay
in the first place.
in Arbiter Hall for so long.
Forget it.
It's better to leave.
He'll be safe.
I'm so sleepy.
My lord.
She has recovered.
So the reason she can't totally recover
is because she's worried about my safety?
Shangque.
Tell me.
If she had known
I was Dongfang Qingcang
from the beginning,
would she have changed her mind
about the Moon Tribe
and risked her life to save me?
Well…
Forget it.
I don't even know that myself.
Why should I ask you?
My lord.
Why don't we let her
fix the Destiny Book now?
Let her sleep first.
Let's talk about it tomorrow.
Yes.
Little Flower Spirit.
This Bone Orchid is transformed
from my blood.
To repay you,
I'll give it to you now.
When you're in danger,
it can protect you.
From now on,
no one can hurt you
even if I'm not by your side.
My lord, Changheng is here.
Changheng?
Why did he come to Haishi?
I don't know.
However, the news of the evil spirit
in Haishi
has spread across the three realms.
I'm afraid he's here
because he got the news.
My lord, what should we do?
Since he's here,
we should meet him.
Yes.
The God of War in Shuiyuntian
came to Haishi
to buy something
or sell something?
I came here
to ask you something.
Lord of Haishi.
Do you recognize this?
Evil spirit?
Yes.
Not long ago,
it hurt a fairy in Shuiyuntian.
As far as I know,
the evil spirit is related to Haishi.
People here only talk about business
and never make enemies.
It seems that
you're suspecting Haishi.
The evil spirit first appeared in Haishi.
Then Liufang Pavilion was in chaos
and suffered casualties.
Why is that?
Do you know
that information in Haishi
costs money?
However,
I can make an exception
for Lord Changheng.
Why?
The appearance of the evil spirit
caused chaos in Haishi
is all because of a mysterious man
who trespassed in Haishi.
A mysterious man?
That mysterious man
has unfathomable power.
He not only brought the evil spirit
to Haishi,
but also destroyed
the foundation of Haishi.
Recently, Haishi has been chaotic.
You mean
this evil spirit was produced
by that mysterious man?
Dieyi.
Hellfire?
That's right.
Among the three realms,
except Dongfang Qingcang
who was sealed 30,000 years ago,
no one can manipulate Hellfire.
Sorry for my offense today.
I'll apologize another day.
Goodbye.
By the way,
when the mysterious man left Haishi,
he took a Shuiyuntian fairy with him.
Who?
It is said to be
a nameless orchid plant spirit.
Thank you.
My lord,
why did you tell Changheng
about Dongfang Qingqing?
Dongfang Qingqing has incredible power.
If he stays by the fairy's side,
we can't do anything.
But if we join hands with Changheng,
we might be able to defeat him.
I drank too much last night.
Gosh.
I'm going to be late for the ceremony.
My lord,
shouldn't we stop her
and let her fix the Destiny Book?
Today is the ceremony of assigning posts.
It's also the day she becomes a fairy.
But…
What does this have to do
with fixing the Destiny Book?
She has been waiting 1,000 years
for this day.
I don’t want to disappoint her.
ARBITER HALL
My lord, someone is here.
It’s Changheng.
I didn't plan to kill him,
but he's courting death.
Dongfang Qingcang.
It's really you.
Let’s begin.
There are many fairies in Shuiyuntian.
After the war between the two tribes,
according to the fairies' real bodies,
Lord Dong divided them
into the eight-immortal system,
which are Heaven, Earth, Thunder, Water,
Fire, Wind, Lake, and Mountain.
You have passed the examination.
Today, the Great Turtle will check
your real bodies
and assign posts to you.
- Yes.
Fairy Yuanwu.
Thunder, Fengbo Hall.
Fairy Orchid.
THE GREAT TURTLE
It turns out to be an old friend.
An old friend?
My ancient god, Xuanwu,
do you know me?
Yes.
I read that
you know all living creatures
in this world.
You are special.
Me? Why?
Joy and sorrow, parting and reunion.
All living beings in the world
have thousands of fates.
But you only have one fate.
God, I don't understand what you mean.
When you understand,
you'll begin to bear your destiny.
What destiny?
My old friend,
take care.
It has been so long.
What's going on?
What's taking so long?
Did something happen?
Is everything okay?
The result is overdue.
Why is there nothing?
Isn't she a plant spirit?
- Yes.
- I don't know.
So she should be in Lake or Mountain.
Why can't she be identified?
This has never happened before.
Aunt Sansheng, is there any problem?
Fairy Yuanwu.
One more time, please.
There it is.
What's wrong with Orchid?
Yes, what's wrong?
Fairy Orchid.
Try it again.
What's going on?
- What happened?
- What is that?
Is she not a fairy?
- What happened?
- So strange.
Sansheng,
check her real body.
Yes.
What is this?
- I've never seen it before.
- What is this?
What is this?
Strange. I've never seen it before.
So what is it?
I'm an orchid plant.
How is that possible?
Your real body is not an orchid plant.
And you're not in
the eight-immortal system of Shuiyuntian.
Orchid isn't a fairy?
She's not a flower spirit?
If you're neither an immortal nor a human,
you're from the Moon Tribe.
- The Moon Tribe?
- How can that be?
- What's wrong?
- The Moon Tribe?
- How could I be from the Moon Tribe?
Master told me I was an orchid seed
she brought from Yunmeng Lake.
She planted me in the Arbiter Hall.
Aunt Sansheng, you saw me transform.
I'm not from the Moon Tribe.
That orchid seed must be your disguise.
Guards!
I'm not from the Moon Tribe.
I'm an orchid plant.
There must be a mistake.
This is…
What's that?
That's…
Hellfire.
Dongfang Qingcang, where are you escaping?
Escape?
I just don't want to destroy
her Arbiter Hall.
Hellfire?
It's indeed Dongfang Qingcang's Hellfire.
I don't know what happened.
Tell me, where is Dongfang Qingcang?
Where is Dongfang Qingcang?
I don't know.
Do you want to die?
I know what you want to ask.
But what's most important
is to catch Dongfang Qingcang.
Go tell Lord Yunzhong.
Where is Dongfang Qingcang?
Orchid, tell us.
If you don't tell us, you'll die.
Her real body is unknown.
I think she's a spy from the Moon Tribe.
I'm not from the Moon Tribe.
I'm not a spy.
I don't know anything.
Why would Dongfang Qingcang's Hellfire
protect you?
I really don’t know.
How dare you
hurt my woman?
Dongfang Qingcang.
You are Dongfang Qingcang?
You lied to me.
I never lied to you.
Why did you save me?
I told you
your life is mine.
With me,
no one can hurt you.
No!
If anyone dares to stop me,
I will destroy Shuiyuntian
and kill everyone.
I'll avenge
the shame of the seal
for 30,000 years
and the oppression of Cangyan Sea.
Put her down.
How dare you
stop me?
Get out of my way.
I won't let you take her away.
I don't want to kill you today.
Step aside.
I said step aside!
Step aside!
Put her down!
Stop!
Do you want to save her
or your Shuiyuntian?
Lord Changheng!
My lord!
The Four-River Pearl controls Shuiyuntian.
Rivers Xiao, Xiang, Li, and Yuan
are the source.
If we don't make up for it,
the water will flow backward.
The whole Shuiyuntian and Yunmeng Lake
will be in misery.
OBLIVION RIVER
Why is she still unconscious?
My lord,
she was poisoned by Lord Yunzhong's
Xuanshuang Whip.
And the cold Oblivion River
prevents her from recovering.
How can I cure her?
My lord, please calm down.
The most important thing now
is to warm her up.
But the Oblivion River is extremely cold.
Only your Hellfire can…
Go ahead and explore the way.
Yes.
You…
Are you afraid of me?
Where are we?
This is the Oblivion River,
the boundary of two tribes.
Do you want to take me to Cangyan Sea?
Moon Supreme, I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
I shouldn't have listened to rumors
and made fun of you.
I even asked you to do chores.
I also said
you paid no attention to hygiene.
I'm sorry.
I even said you're a homeless dog.
Moon Supreme.
If there's nothing else to do,
I'll take my leave.
You don't have to see me off.
I can go back to Shuiyuntian myself.
Back to Shuiyuntian?
You are a traitor now.
Do you want them to kill you?
I'm not a traitor.
I will explain to them.
Shuiyuntian is my home.
I want to go home.
That's over.
I'm not a traitor.
My lord.
Lord Xunfeng is fighting
with the two kings of You in Wind Plain.
They've conquered Silver Lake
and are heading to Ninth You.
How long can Xunfeng last?
I'm afraid
he won't survive tonight.
The kings have always been ambitious
and covet
the position of the Moon Supreme.
They didn't dare to do anything
because they were afraid of your power.
But since you were told dead,
Lord Xunfeng became the new Moon Supreme.
The Kings of North and South You
kept starting civil wars to replace him.
If we go back late,
Lord Xunfeng may be…
- Go to Wind Plain.
- Yes.
Keep your eyes open
and have a look.
I'm not that kind of guy
who can be beaten up
or killed by you immortals.